<Publish>
  <!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
  <ModId Value="100369" />
  <!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
  <DisplayName Value="Stash It" />
  <!--Short description of the mod-->
  <ShortDescription Value="Stash all logs automatically when close" />
  <!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
  <!--LongDescription Value="Stash all logs automatically when close" /-->
  <LongDescription># Stash It

"Stash It" is a lightweight and efficient tool designed to ensure your game logs are preserved and organized, even after your game exits unexpectedly. Whether you’re a developer debugging your game or a power user interested in reviewing detailed runtime behavior, Stash It keeps all the logs safe and accessible.

## Features

- Automatic Log Archiving: Automatically saves and compresses logs upon game exit, ensuring no critical information is lost.
- Seamless Integration: Runs silently in the background with minimal performance overhead, integrating smoothly with your game's lifecycle.
- Crash Resilience: Captures logs even during unexpected crashes, providing vital insights into game behavior at the moment of failure.

Save directory: %AppData%\..\LocalLow\Colossal Order\Cities Skylines II\ModsData\.StashIt

## How It Works

When your game exits, Stash It scans predefined log directories, gathers relevant files, and compresses them into a timestamped archive. This ensures that every session's logs are securely stored for review, debugging, or archiving.

## Who Is It For?

- Game Developers: Simplifies debugging by preserving detailed runtime logs across sessions.
- QA Testers: Ensures that no issue or crash report is missing critical data.
- Power Users: Allows advanced players to review game logs and performance metrics for optimization or community reporting.</LongDescription>
  <!--Thumbnail-->
  <Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
  <!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
  <Screenshot Value="" />
  <!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
  <Tag Value="" />
  <!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
  <ForumLink Value="" />
  <!--Version of the mod-->
  <ModVersion Value="1.0.0-build3" />
  <!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
  <GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
  <!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
  <Dependency Id="" />
  <!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
  <ChangeLog># 1.0.0

- make PMOD happier</ChangeLog>
  <!--ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog-->
  <!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon, buymeacoffee, kofi, crowdin, gitlab-->
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/baka-gourd/StashIt" />
  <ExternalLink Type="patreon" Url="https://www.patreon.com/Nullpinter" />
</Publish>